<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../input-cache/schemas-r5/fhir-single.xsd">
	
	<div id="Categorie" class="tabcontent">
	<h3>Document profiles</h3>
	<div>
	<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-document-immunization-administration.html">CH VACD Immunization Administration Document</a> Definition of the bundle for the immunization administration document. This document is allowed to be used in context of the Swiss EPR but can also used in context of data exchange next to the Swiss EPR.</li>
	<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-document-vaccination-record.html">CH VACD Vaccination Record Document</a> Definition of the bundle for the vaccination record document. This document is allowed to be used in context of the Swiss EPR but can also used in context of data exchange next to the Swiss EPR.</li>
	<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-recommendation-request-message.html">CH VACD Immunization Recommendation Request Message</a> Definition of the bundle for the immunization recommendation request.</li>
	<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-recommendation-response-message.html">CH VACD Immunization Recommendation Response Message</a> Definition of the bundle for the immunization recommendation response.</li>
	</div>

	<h3>Composition profiles</h3>
	<div>
	<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-composition-immunization-administration.html">CH VACD Immunization Administration Composition</a>Definition of the composition for the immunization administration document. This composition is allowed to be used in context of the Swiss EPR but can also used in context of data exchange next to the Swiss EPR.</li>
	<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-composition-vaccination-record.html">CH VACD VaccinationRecord Composition</a> Definition of the composition for the vaccination record document. This composition is allowed to be used in context of the Swiss EPR but can also used in context of data exchange next to the Swiss EPR.</li>
	<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-recommendation-request-messageheader.html">CH VACD Immunization Recommendation Request MessageHeader</a> Definition of the MessageHeader for the immunization recommendation request message.</li>
	<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-recommendation-response-messageheader.html">CH VACD Immunization Recommendation Response MessageHeader</a> Definition of the composition for the immunization recommendation response message.</li>
	</div>
		
	<h3>Common profiles</h3>
	<div>
		<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-immunization.html">CH VACD Immunization</a>Definition of the immunization part for all documents, except recommendation request and response documents.</li>
		<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-medical-problems.html">CH VACD Medical Problems</a> Definition of the medical problems part for all documents, except recommendation request and response documents.</li>
		<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-pastillnesses.html">CH VACD Past Illness</a> Definition of the past illness part for all documents, except recommendation request and response documents.</li>
		<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-allergyintolerances.html">CH VACD AllergyIntolerance</a> Definition of the AllergyIntolerance part for vaccination record documents.</li>
		<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-laboratory-serology.html">CH VACD Laboratory And Serology</a> Definition of the labor and serology part for all documents, except recommendation request and response documents.</li>
		<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-immunization-recommendation.html">CH VACD Immunization Recommendations</a> Definition of the immunization recommendation part for all documents, except recommendation request and response documents.</li>
		<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-medication-for-immunization.html">CH VACD Medication For Immunization</a> Definition of the medication for immunization.</li>
		<li><a href="StructureDefinition-ch-vacd-basic-immunization.html">CH VACD Basic Immunization</a> Condition to declare Basic Immunization done by one single condition for DTPa or Polio. This is for cases the patient does not have a vaccination certificate to declare it, but knows that it is done.</li>
	</div>

	</div>

	<div id="All" class="tabcontent" style="visibility: hidden">
		{% include list-profiles.xhtml %}
	</div>
	
</div>